

### Sabino Rotondi

• Home: Via Nicola Salvi, 57, 83042, Atripalda, Italy

**Website:** <a href="https://github.com/sabinorotondi">https://github.com/sabinorotondi</a>

LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/sabinorotondi/

**Gender:** Male **Date of birth:** 19/05/2000 **Nationality:** Italian

#### **ABOUT ME**

Front-End Developer, experienced with: HTML, CSS, JavaScript, ReactJS, NextJS, TypeScript, and a number of frameworks, including Bootstrap, Material UI, Tailwind, and AntD. When I first began, I was working as a bartender. In my spare time, I studied frontend development on a variety of platforms, including "Udemy, Codecademy, and Develhope."

#### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

## [ 2019 - 2023 ] **Front End Developer**

Front-End Developer. I utilize the React library, as well as two major frameworks: Tailwind CSS and Material UI. To enhance React, I use a variety of technologies, including "Vite and Nextls." Nextls is my preferred option. It reflects the future and is significantly more dynamic in terms of application development. I use "Git" for version management. I like to stay updated on the technologies I use, and I have a strong drive to learn new methods of working. I prefer working in groups and comparing myself to other devs.

# [ 2019 – 2020 ] **Front End Developer**

#### **Freelance**

Worked on projects using React|S Library and Bootstrap framework. I have built personal portfolios, dashboards and stores.

# [ 2021 – 2022 ] **Front End Developer**

#### **Freelance**

Worked on Web Applications using React|S and Next|S, using GIT for version management and two frameworks (Tailwind CSS and MaterialUI). I have built personal portfolios, dashboards and stores

#### **EDUCATION AND TRAINING**

[2021]

### **Codecademy - Frontend Engineer**

Address: Italy

[ 2021 ] Codecademy - Fullstack Engineer

**Address:** Italy

[ 2022 ] **Develhope - Fullstack Web Developer** 

**Address:** Italy

[2019] **Diploma - Liceo scientifico** 

**Address:** Italy